LAUGHING MAN FANSUBS
Angels and demons were circling over me,
Crossing a brambly path of stars and milky ways.
He who does not perceive his calling,
does not know true happiness.
Watch in awe! Watch in awe!
Flying in glory, Flying in glory
I am calling, calling now.
Spirits rise and falling.
To be with you longer
Calling, calling...
in the depth of longing
To stay myself longer
The flow may shallow you, flying in glory
Murai Vaccine Recipients List
Oh, no.
The
Deleted
Medicine
It's stable.
Next?
Sectors B-14 through 16.
The extracted memory
corresponds with her testimony.
This means that she is not lying.
So, she was only doing the paperwork and
was unaware of the document's import.
However, it has been confirmed that the
memory-overwrite of the witnesses concerning Nanao A
was executed by an official order from the Ministry
of Health, Labour and Welfare that she issued.
If so, wouldn't it be reasonable to assume that
her superiors at the Ministry are involved?
Moreover, the Ministry was also
being hacked by the vocational centre
where I conducted my failed
undercover investigation.
I'm telling you, there is something in the Ministry
regarding the Laughing Man case that they want to keep hidden!
Or, it could be that there is a third party who wishes us
to assume as much, and is mediating this whole affair.
If so, it's all the more reason to attempt
another dive into the Ministry's database.
Ishikawa and Bomer have already conducted enough
salvage operations to make themselves sick.
There was no record of
tampering anywhere, either.
In information theft, what is stolen is not lost,
so we just have to try another method.
The Ministry of Health,
Labour and Welfare does indeed appear suspicious.
However, if we were to conduct an official
investigation, our intentions would be laid bare.
If we proceed with a formal
investigation in spite of this drawback,
we'll need to secure a suitable payoff.
Sorry, I know it's dinner time...
Try the potatoes. They're really good.
Yep.
I think they turned out well today, don't you?
Yep, they did.
Catcher in the Rye
JD Salinger
"If I am somewhere where no one knows me,"
"and I also know no one,"
"what I thought I'd do there was,"
"I'd become one of those deaf-mutes."
"Become..."
"Should become..."
"Should I become?"
Could it be...?!
I heard that you're pursuing the Salinger link?
Yes.
It is true
that he left behind a short story titled "The Laughing
Man", and that there are quite a few people out there
who have pointed out the similarities
between that work and the Laughing Man case.
However, the task force has already completed their
analysis of that work's relationship to the case.
I don't think an interpretation of that
work will provide the key to this case.
Art imitates life.
If so, the opposite may be true as well.
I cannot help but think that the youth I met at
the vocational centre was the real Laughing Man.
There have been many who have been
suspected of being the Laughing Man.
Given that, what is your basis for
believing that that youth was the real one?
Major, you know what the words written
on the Laughing Man's symbol mean, right?
"What I thought I'd do there was,"
"I'd become one of those deaf-mutes."
It's supposedly drawn from the 25th
chapter of "The Catcher in the Rye".
Yes, I mentioned it in my report,
but I found a part of it in
the vocational centre as well.
At first, I was convinced that it was
taken word-for-word from the novel,
but the passage I found continued after
"I'd become one of those deaf-mutes".
"Or should I?" As in, should he become one or not.
That was added to the original text.
Wasn't he questioning himself...
whether he should break his
silence and rejoin the world?
Don't you feel this way sometimes too, Major?
When you try to imitate a
cultural figure that you like,
you try to mimic him or her
as much as possible, right?
But the youth who changed Salinger's passage
was able to do so without qualms
because he was the original.
That reasoning is quite dependent
on your personal opinion, isn't it?
You do realise that it doesn't hold water
as the basis for a theory, don't you?
Even though the Laughing Man is
classified as a class A+ hacker,
This Morning's
Weather
he physically abducted President
SERANO and held a gun to his head.
He is a criminal whose anachronistic
methods do not match his abilities.
It could be that even though
he is an expert hacker...
no, because of it, the Laughing Man did
not value rewritable electronic data.
If so, it may be that what he sought
was data preserved in physical form,
or, in other words,
information preserved in a paper medium.
And you would like to confirm
that with your own eyes.
Yes.
I was thinking of stopping you if revenge over
what happened at the centre was your motive,
but it could be that your "ghost"
is beginning to whisper to you.
Permission granted.
Do what you want.
I'll tell the Chief.
Thank you.
Ministry of Health, Labour and Welfare
How is it going?
I managed to finish,
although the answer has yet to emerge.
I thought you'd give up after
the first two or three days,
but you're pretty persistent.
Well, it's my job, after all.
Oh, sorry about the last time.
Well, it had to be done.
It's my job, after all.
Here it is!
What is?
Or rather, what should be here, isn't.
The list of those who were
vaccinated by the Murai vaccine.
It's the only one that is missing.
You're right. I wonder if it
was misplaced in another box.
What is this Murai vaccine?
It is a specialised medication that is
effective in treating cyberbrain sclerosis.
When it was announced, micromachine treatment
had yet to become commercially viable,
so it created quite a stir.
But in the end,
it was never approved for medical use.
Why?
It seems that the vaccine
did have a certain effect,
but no one understood how it worked.
It somehow worked...
But if a concrete cause cannot
be linked to a drug's effects,
it cannot be approved for medical use.
I see.
That is why the drug evaluation
committee could not easily approve it.
Besides, Dr. Murai was not an
expert on cyberbrain sclerosis.
I guess it was a coincidental discovery.
Even so, It was not as though
everything went smoothly from the start.
A Magic Cure
The Murai Vaccine
A specific cure for Cyberbrain Sclerosis
I heard that he completed the vaccine
after a grueling period of trial and error.
And the list of subjects who have
been vaccinated is missing...
I wonder how long it's been missing.
I don't think stealing it
would benefit anyone, though.
Can you think of anyone who might
find value in a file like that?
Let me think...
If I had to come up with a name,
it'd be the Sunflower Society.
"Sunflower"...?
I need to write up my report; it's due tomorrow.
2019.
At a time when cyberbrain
implantation was just becoming common,
a certain cyberbrain disorder of mysterious
origins caused a stir in the medical field.
Sections of the brain that received
cyberbrain implants gradually hardened
and eventually lead to brain death.
The disorder was later named cyberbrain sclerosis.
While the probability of getting
this disorder was not high,
anyone with cyberbrain implants was susceptible.
Since no cure had been found,
following tuberculosis, cancer, and HIV,
it was called the incurable disease of the 21st century.
Please enter keywords.
Murai Vaccine
The Murai vaccine, developed as a specific cure by
Dr. Murai Chitose, is a tumor-suppressing agent.
However, medical experts at the time consisted
largely of micromachine treatment advocates.
The vaccine treatment developed by Dr. Murai
was conceptually behind the times,
and the majority felt that allowing his research
would delay completion of the concurrent
research on micromachine treatment.
Perhaps because of such concerns,
approval of the Murai vaccine was delayed.
Dr. Murai, who hoped for the approval of
his vaccine treatment until the very end,
died an unfulfilled death
in February 2021 at age 68,
without witnessing the decision
of the drug evaluation committee.
However, in April 2021,
the Murai vaccine was suddenly approved for special use
by select individuals, after initially being rejected.
This approval was not made public,
and patients who used the
vaccine do not officially exist.
Even now, there are those who
are interested in the situation.
The Sunflower Society.
It is an NPO that supports individuals who file
suit against the government and large corporations.
They demanded disclosure of
information on the Murai vaccine
How to support victims of drug-induced harm
Symposium on Cyber Sclerosis
Opening Remarks from our Representatives
and those who have received the vaccine from
government agencies on multiple occasions in the past.
However, the Ministry of Health,
Labour and Welfare used the individual privacy
act as a shield to reject their demands.
Perhaps my belief that there was a connection between the
Sunflower Society and the Laughing Man was... premature.
SUNFLOWER SOCIETY
This mark...
I see... You have indeed done your research.
Are you a freelance journalist?
Actually, my father passed away a few
months ago from cyberbrain sclerosis.
He received micromachine
treatment until the very end.
I found out abut your Society's activities later,
along with the existence of the Murai vaccine.
I see.
I am sorry for your loss.
If only someone had told me about the
vaccine's efficacy at an earlier time...
maybe my father would have survived.
When I think about that, I can't let it go.
I didn't have the slightest interest
in this sort of thing before.
However, if I'm to help those who suffer
from the same affliction that my father did,
I will need to use my profession.
I understand how you feel. Many others in
the past have reached the same conclusion.
However, they all failed.
Why is that?
The micromachine lobby is too strong.
It controls too many people in too many places.
So it is true.
Fortunately, however, I know a lot of
people in the entertainment industry.
From what I hear, there are several in the
industry who are secretly receiving the Murai vaccine.
It is difficult to spread
stories of a serious nature.
In order to spread the story, isn't a...
scandal necessary?
It seems that your visit here was well planned.
To tell you the truth,
we have obtained a certain file.
A file?
Confirmed contact with the bar association.
That's crude encryption.
I wonder if those amateurs are
underestimating us... the fools.
Two minutes until arrival.
List of Murai Vaccine Recipients
Well, please take a look.
Oh, is this the famous author...?
Yes. There are also artist, former athletes...
This one is a professor at Hamada Medical School.
I'm amazed... There are even names of politicians.
Yes... an even more significant figure
has been treated with the vaccine.
Can you pick him out?
Imakurusu Hisashi... the Chairman of
the Central Drug Evaluation Committee!
The Chairman, who did not approve the
Murai vaccine, is himself dependent on it?
This file was sent to us
yesterday by Imakurusu himself.
What does this all mean?
Imakurusu said that he had grown tired of
keeping his silence after all these years.
He had accepted its efficacy, yet had to
deliberately suppress it due to superior influences.
He promised that he would testify in court
about the reasons that only he knows.
The central figure of the
drug evaluation committee
said that he would testify regarding the
deliberate suppression of the vaccine?
Yes.
This time, we will win!
The Narcotics Department's assault team!
Come on, guys. Kill them already.
We can look for the target at our leisure later.
First, kill them all!
The attackers are affiliated with the
Ministry of Health, Labour and Welfare.
Then, this file is...!
You have to run, now!
These troops are professionals.
Who are you...?
I'm with Public Safety.
This way is still safe.
I'm entrusting you with this file!
Make sure what happened
here gets out to the public.
Someone needs to tell the
truth that is in this file!
No, that's your responsibility!
You have a better chance to escape!
Hey, how's that room going?
In any case, let's go.
Oops, our men are down.
Well, we need to take some hits, too.
That's what I call reality.
Right?!
Find the corpse.
A cyborg!
Mmm, this is getting interesting.
There is a survivor.
Get the hell over here!
Hey, hey. If you don't run
quickly, I'll shoot you!
Damn it...
Isn't that our truck?
Go finish him off!
Chief, our mission is complete.
However, the file is a copy.
What?!
We know the origin.
HISASHI IMAKURUSU
SUNFLOWER SOCIETY
DOCUMENTS (COPY)
It was Imakurusu.
Are you the one who has the original?!
No! It wasn't me!
Please believe me!
The copy that the Sunflower
Society had was sent from you!
I hope you haven't allowed guilt to overcome
you, after all these years...
What would be the benefit of doing such a thing?
Someone is just using my name!
What about the fact that your name is on
the list of those who received the vaccine?
Answer me!
Do you have cyberbrain sclerosis?!
Yes... from a long time ago.
It is already in its terminal phase.
Why didn't you come to me for advice?!
You made huge mistake leaving
your name on the list!
I apologise.
However, as we thought, the Murai vaccine works.
We knew that!
You will be dealt with!
What shall we do? Eliminate him?
Shut up. I'll contact you later.
Terminal phase, did he say?
The fool...
Damn it...
Maybe I should've become a cyborg, too...
Major...
Chief...
I've been hit...
I'm so tired...
Rain?
She's so cold and human
It's something humans do
She stays so cold in her soul, she's so number 9
She's incredible math
Just incredible math
And is she really human?
She says there's something new
But wake a lithium flower, just about to bloom
I smell lithium now
Smelling lithium now
How... is she what she doesn't say
She doesn't say
How is she when she doesn't suffer
I wonder what she does when she wakes up
When she wakes up